=Deity of Love= =Episode 2=
= إله الحب = = الحلقة 2 =
(What happened?)
(ماذا حدث؟)
(Why is there a girl here?)
(لماذا توجد فتاة هنا؟)
(She wakes up.)
(تستيقظ).
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I'm Li Xiuning from Qingyun Valley.
أنا Li Xiuning من وادي Qingyun.
Miss, are you feeling good?
آنسة ، هل تشعرين بتحسن؟
Where are we?
اين نحن؟
The land of Jinghu Lake.
أرض بحيرة جينغو.
Miss, who are you?
انتي مين انت
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
(Xiaoqing! Live on!)
(شياو تشينغ! عش!)
I...
أنا...
I'm Xiaoqing.
أنا شياو تشينغ.
(Xiaoqing.)
(شياو تشينغ.)
(Who is it?)
(من هذا؟)
Miss, are you okay?
انسة هل انت بخير
Why can't I remember?
لماذا لا اتذكر؟
Let's go out first.
دعنا نخرج أولا.
The land of Jinghu Lake.
أرض بحيرة جينغو.
Your Excellency.
امتيازك.
Just now,
الآن،
something unusual happened in Jinghu Lake.
حدث شيء غير عادي في بحيرة جينغو.
You go there and investigate first.
تذهب هناك وتحقق أولا.
Jinghu Lake
بحيرة جينغو
is where the Snake Demon has been sealed.
هو المكان الذي تم فيه ختم الأفعى الشيطانية.
Do...
يفعل...
Do we need finish the selection in Jinghu Lake earlier?
هل نحتاج إلى إنهاء التحديد في بحيرة Jinghu في وقت سابق؟
No.
رقم.
But if the Snake Demon come out,
ولكن إذا خرج شيطان الأفعى ،
she would wreak havoc in the human world.
سوف تعيث فسادا في العالم البشري.
At that time...
فى ذلك التوقيت...
If you fear demons,
إذا كنت تخشى الشياطين ،
how can you become a demon hunter?
كيف يمكنك أن تصبح صياد شياطين؟
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
Green Sanke Demon.
شيطان سانكي الأخضر.
This time,
هذا الوقت،
I will never let you get out of my hands again.
لن أدعك تخرج من يدي مرة أخرى.
It's he.
إنه هو.
It's they
إنهم هم
who made such a big noise just now.
الذي أحدث ضجة كبيرة الآن.
How dare they bother us?
كيف يجرؤون على مضايقتنا؟
Kill him.
اقتله.
Demons.
شياطين.
You are so lucky
أنت محظوظ جدا
to come across us.
ليصادفنا.
Lucky.
سعيد الحظ.
If you are sensible,
إذا كنت عاقلًا ،
give us your valuable things.
أعطنا أشياءك القيمة.
Give them to us.
أعطهم لنا.
Otherwise...
خلاف ذلك...
Otherwise, hey hey.
خلاف ذلك ، مهلا.
Otherwise what?
وإلا ماذا؟
Stop talking too much.
توقف عن الحديث كثيرا.
Wrong spell.
تعويذة خاطئة.
Why can't I get my hand away from yours?
لماذا لا أستطيع إبعاد يدي عن يدك؟
You said I should just tie them together.
قلت إنني يجب أن أربطهم معًا.
Hey,
يا،
we're demons not the Matchmaker.
نحن شياطين ولسنا صانع الثقاب.
Tie what?
ربط ماذا؟
Demons, break the spell.
الشياطين ، كسر التعويذة.
Call me Master Da first.
اتصل بي سيد دا أولا.
And then call me Master Er.
ثم اتصل بي السيد إيه.
Sir, Sir.
سيدي سيدي.
We are doing this for a living.
نحن نفعل هذا من أجل لقمة العيش.
Yes, I have an elder demon
نعم ، لدي شيطان كبير
and a young demon to support.
وشيطان صغير لدعمه.
When did you see a woman?
متى رأيت امرأة؟
Why don't I know that?
لماذا لا اعرف ذلك؟
How can I tell you?
كيف استطيع اخبارك؟
Demons,
الشياطين
I only repeat one more time.
أكرر مرة واحدة فقط.
Hurry and break the spell.
على عجل وكسر التعويذة.
Otherwise...
خلاف ذلك...
I won't tell you.
لن أخبرك.
(Help!)
(مساعدة!)
(Brother Ning Yu. Brother Ning Yu.)
(الأخ نينغ يو. الأخ نينغ يو.)
(You want to catch me?)
(هل تريد الإمساك بي؟)
(I'll kill you first.)
(سأقتلك أولاً.)
Miss Xiaoqing.
ملكة جمال شياو تشينغ.
Watch out.
احذر.
The hooked jade?
اليشم مدمن مخدرات؟
Oh no.
أوه لا.
(Humph, I'll spare you today.)
(همف ، سأوفر عليك اليوم.)
The heart seal is starting to break?
هل ختم القلب بدأ ينكسر؟
Does the seal loosen again?
هل يخفف الختم مرة أخرى؟
If this continues,
إذا استمر هذا ،
you will meet your end.
سوف تقابل نهايتك.
I'm all right.
انا بخير.
It's a pity that the Peach Blossom Demon ran away.
إنه لأمر مؤسف أن هرب شيطان زهرة الخوخ.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Why did you grab brother Xiuning's sealing jade pendant?
لماذا أخذت قلادة اليشم المختومة للأخ Xiuning؟
That's my jade pendant.
هذه قلادة اليشم الخاصة بي.
You bandit.
أنت اللصوص.
It is obviously brother Xiuning's sealing jade pendant.
من الواضح أنه قلادة اليشم المختومة للأخ Xiuning.
How could it be yours?
كيف يمكن أن يكون لك؟
Brother Xiuning.
الأخ Xiuning.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
A demon cast a spell upon us.
ألقى الشيطان تعويذة علينا.
Why is your jade pendant the same as mine?
لماذا قلادة اليشم الخاصة بك هي نفسها لي؟
It's a jade pendant I have worn since I was young.
إنها قلادة من اليشم أرتديها منذ أن كنت صغيراً.
Do you have memory about yours?
هل لديك ذاكرة عنك؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
If you can't remember, forget it.
إذا كنت لا تستطيع التذكر ، انس الأمر.
Hey,
يا،
why are you tied to my brother?
لماذا انت مرتبط باخي
My name is not hey.
اسمي ليس مهلا.
I'm Xiao Qing.
أنا شياو تشينغ.
I don't know why we are tied together.
لا أعرف لماذا نحن مرتبطون ببعضنا البعض.
It's so suspicious that you show up suddenly
من المريب جدًا أن تظهر فجأة
in this place full of demons.
في هذا المكان المليء بالشياطين.
You're a demon.
أنت شيطان.
Ning Yu,
نينغ يو
calm down.
هدء من روعك.
Is there any demonic energy?
هل هناك أي طاقة شيطانية؟
Xiaoqing is not a demon.
شياو تشينغ ليس شيطان.
The demon has various images.
الشيطان لديه صور مختلفة.
I agree with you.
أنا أتفق معك.
(Are they saying
(هل يقولون
I am a demon?)
أنا شيطان؟)
It's a pity that the Peach Blossom Demon escaped.
إنه لأمر مؤسف أن هرب شيطان زهرة الخوخ.
Li Xiuning,
لي شيونينغ ،
the top priority now
الأولوية القصوى الآن
is to break this spell first.
هو كسر هذه التعويذة أولاً.
And then recover yourself.
ثم تسترد نفسك.
Let's go back to the inn.
دعنا نعود إلى النزل.
Hey.
يا.
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Hum.
همم.
I don't care where you come from,
لا يهمني من أين أتيت
but never try to take my brother Xiuning.
لكن لا تحاول أبدًا أن تأخذ أخي Xiuning.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(حق إعادة بث المسرحية على الإنترنت ملك لي.) (شركة Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co.، Ltd.)